{
  "title": "Periodic Table (of Elements)",
  "ref": "https://www.unicode.org/charts/PDF/U1700.pdf",
  "test": [
      {
      "id": "Introduction",
      "answer": "C",
      "question": "<p>This Periodic Table test bank has 118 elements.<HR> <p><B>‚ü≥IndexFlip buttons</B> <p>Restart:‚óÄÔ∏è‚óÄÔ∏è <p>Previous:‚óÄÔ∏è <p>Random:üé≤ <p>Next:‚ñ∂Ô∏è<HR><p> <B>About<\/B><ul><li> <A HREF=\"https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzqFPv5zpmmyu3EYc9IzNJ8fUONPtsZ7O\">IndexFlip Demo Videos<\/A><li><A HREF=\"https://github.com/brianjester/brianjester.github.com/issues\">Need to file a bug\/feature request?<\/A><\/ul>",
      "A": "",
      "B": "",
      "C": "",
      "D": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q1",
      "answer": "A",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;H&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Hydrogen",
      "B": "Helium",
      "C": "Hafnium",
      "D": "Hassium"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q2",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;He&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Hydrogen",
      "B": "Helium",
      "C": "Hafnium",
      "D": "Hassium"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q3",
      "answer": "C",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;Li&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Lead",
      "B": "Lanthanum",
      "C": "Lithium",
      "D": "Lutetium"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q4",
      "answer": "D",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;Be&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Barium",
      "B": "Bismuth",
      "C": "Boron",
      "D": "Berylium"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q5",
      "answer": "C",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;B&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Barium",
      "B": "Bismuth",
      "C": "Boron",
      "D": "Berylium"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q6",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;C&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Chlorine",
      "B": "Carbon",
      "C": "Copper",
      "D": "Cobalt"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q7",
      "answer": "D",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;N&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Neodymium",
      "B": "Nickel",
      "C": "Neon",
      "D": "Nitrogen"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q8",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;O&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Osmium",
      "B": "Oxygen",
      "C": "Oganesson",
      "D": "Gold"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q9",
      "answer": "C",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;F&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Fermium",
      "B": "Flerovium",
      "C": "Fluorine",
      "D": "Francium"
    },
    {
      "id": "T1Q10",
      "answer": "C",
      "question": "What element is this?<br><br><span class=\"periodic-text\" style=\"font-family: monospace; font-size: 400%; vertical-align: 1.5ex; background-color: coral; border:3px solid; white-space: pre-wrap; text-align: center;\">&nbsp;Ne&nbsp;<\/span>",
      "A": "Neodymium",
      "B": "Nickel",
      "C": "Neon",
      "D": "Nitrogen"
    }

  ]
}